# Erhan Güven

GAME DEVELOPER

### **Details**

+905385162252 erhangvn7@gmail.com

### Links

LinkedIn

Github

#### Skills

Unity

C#

C++

### **Hobbies**

American Football Computer Games

### Languages

Turkish

English

### **Profile**

When I was a child, I always wanted to learn how to make a game. Since then, I'm passionately developing games and I have tried a lot of game engines.

I'm developing games with Unity since 2017 and most of them was multiplayer games. I'm currently a 4th grade Computer Science student.

My profession is Unity and C#. I have also worked with C++ professionally when I was at Masomo. I'm strong at Object Oriented Programming and I have strong math and algorithm skills. I'm also good at planning and managing development process because I worked as a lead in many indie game projects before. Most of the projects that I've worked on were multiplayer so I'm good at making network based games.

I'm also interested in the development of game engines. I've been developing my own game engine for 6 months and I've learned a lot from it by making it's own physics engine, sound engine and networking system. I've also learned computer graphics, threading and dozens of other things by working on this project.

## **Employment History**

## Game Developer, Cappuccino LLC, Izmir

JULY 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2020

I worked as Game Developer here. It was my first job and I improved my C#, OOP and game-prototyping skills here. I was usually choosing hardest game mechanics to improve myself. Back then, hypercasual games were not that simple and the games I worked on were mostly complex and had mechanics that were difficult to develop, so I improved my algorithm skills here.

#### Game Developer, Masomo, Izmir

OCTOBER 2020 - OCTOBER 2021

It was the hardest and most instructive experience in my career. I worked on both Headball 2 and Basketball Arena. I was mainly developing new features and fixing bugs using Cocos2d-x. It was a really good opportunity to upgrade myself to a higher level because It was one of the biggest game companies in Turkey and there were so many good developers out there that taught me a lot. I improved myself at C++ and OOP and how to work on a really big project. I was also dealing with physics and networking.

### Mentor, Global Game Jam

I was a mentor at GGJ 2020. I was helping jammers to fix their problems at their development process.

### **Education**

## **Dokuz Eylül University**

SEPTEMBER 2018 - JUNE 2022

**Computer Science**